Guide to the Dorsey and Whitney, LLP Guantanamo Bay Detention Camp Records TAM.509
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series II: Court Documents, 2004-2008.
  - U.S. District Court: Al Murbati v. Bush - Pleadings re: Respondents' Motion to Dismiss, May 3, 2007-May 14, 2007 (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - U.S. Court of Appeals: Al Odah v. U.S.A. - Holding Case in Abeyance, Jun 20, 2007-Aug 8, 2007 (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - U.S. District Court: Al Murbati v. Bush - Notice of Transfer of Petitioner Al Dossari, Jun 16, 2007 (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - U.S. Court of Appeals: Al Dossari v. Gates: Notice of Transfer of Petitioner Al Dossari, Jul 23, 2007 (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - U.S. District Court: Al Murbati v. Bush: Notice of Transfer of Petitioner Al Murbati, Aug 10, 2007 (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - Supreme Court: Al Odah v. U.S.A. - Brief of Salim Hamdan as Amicus Curiae, Aug 24, 2007 (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - Supreme Court: Al Odah v. U.S.A. - Briefs for Petitioners (I), Aug 2007 (Box 4, Folder 29)
  - Supreme Court: Al Odah v. U.S.A. - Briefs for Petitioners (II), Aug 2007 (Box 4, Folder 30)
  - Supreme Court: Al Odah v. U.S.A. - Joint Appendix, [Aug 2007] (Box 4, Folder 31)
  - Supreme Court: Al Odah v. U.S.A. - Brief for Respondents, Oct 9, 2007-Oct 11, 2007 (Box 4, Folder 32)
  - Supreme Court: Al Odah v. U.S.A. - Reply Briefs for Petitioners, Nov 2007 (Box 4, Folder 33)
  - Supreme Court: Al Odah v. U.S.A. - Motion to File Supplemental Brief and Supplemental Brief for Respondents, Dec 20, 2007-Dec 21, 2007 (Box 4, Folder 34)
  - Supreme Court: Al Odah v. U.S.A. - Supplemental Reply Briefs, Feb 2008 (Box 4, Folder 35)
  - Supreme Court: Al Odah v. U.S.A. - Motion for Leave to File Supplemental Brief and Supplemental Brief for Respondents, Mar 31, 2008 (Box 4, Folder 36)
  - Supreme Court: Al Odah v. U.S.A. - Judgment Vacating Cases, Jun 25, 2008 (Box 4, Folder 37)
  - U.S. District Court: Al Murbati v. Bush - Joint Status Report, Jun 27, 2008 (Box 4, Folder 38)
  - U.S. District Court: In re: Petitioners Seeking Habeas Corpus Relief in Relation to Prior Detentions at Guantanamo Bay, Jul 3, 2008-Jul 14, 2008 (Box 4, Folder 39)
  - U.S. Court of Appeals: Al Dossari v. Gates - Respondents' Renewed Motion to Designate as "Protected Information" Unclassified Information in Record on Review, Sep 18, 2008 (Box 4, Folder 40)
  - U.S. Court of Appeals: Al Murbati v. Bush - Notice of Withdrawal of Appearance of Co-Counsel for Petitioners-Appellees, Oct 29, 2008 (Box 4, Folder 41)
- Series III: Press, 2004-2008.
  - Arabic Language Press, 2005, undated (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Arabic Language Press (with Annotations in English), 2005-2006 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - English Language Press: Bahrain - Bahrain Tribune, 2005-2007 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - English Language Press: Bahrain - Gulf Daily News, 2004 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - English Language Press: Bahrain - Gulf Daily News, Jan 2005-Sep 2005 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - English Language Press: Bahrain - Gulf Daily News, Oct 2005 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - English Language Press: Bahrain - Gulf Daily News, Nov 2005-Dec 2005 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - English Language Press: Bahrain - Gulf Daily News, Jan 2006-Jun 2006 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - English Language Press: Bahrain - Gulf Daily News, Jul 2006-Dec 2006 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - English Language Press: Bahrain - Gulf Daily News, 2007-2008 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - English Language Press: International, 2004-2008 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - English Language Press: United States and United Kingdom - Essays, 2004-2008 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - English Language Press: United States - Various News Sources, 2004-2005 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - English Language Press: United States - Various News Sources, 2006 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - English Language Press: United States - Various News Sources, 2007-2008 (Box 5, Folder 15)